[
  {
    "question": "licka",
    "answer": "cheeks"
  },
  {
    "question": "obraz",
    "answer": "face"
  },
  {
    "question": "nos",
    "answer": "nose"
  },
  {
    "question": "ušesa",
    "answer": "ears"
  },
  {
    "question": "obrvi",
    "answer": "eyebrows"
  },
  {
    "question": "brada",
    "answer": "chin"
  },
  {
    "question": "oči",
    "answer": "eyes"
  },
  {
    "question": "zobje",
    "answer": "teeth"
  },
  {
    "question": "glava",
    "answer": "head"
  },
  {
    "question": "usta",
    "answer": "mouth"
  },
  {
    "question": "rama",
    "answer": "shoulder"
  },
  {
    "question": "roka",
    "answer": "arm"
  },
  {
    "question": "lase",
    "answer": "hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "roka (dlan)",
    "answer": "hand"
  },
  {
    "question": "prst na nogi",
    "answer": "toe"
  },
  {
    "question": "prst na roki",
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "question": "noga",
    "answer": "leg"
  },
  {
    "question": "stopalo",
    "answer": "foot"
  },
  {
    "question": "telo",
    "answer": "body"
  },
  {
    "question": "hrbet",
    "answer": "back"
  },
  {
    "question": "jezik",
    "answer": "tongue"
  },
  {
    "question": "koleno",
    "answer": "knee"
  },
  {
    "question": "želodec",
    "answer": "stomach"
  },
  {
    "question": "trebušček",
    "answer": "belly"
  },
  {
    "question": "trup",
    "answer": "trunk"
  },
  {
    "question": "vrat",
    "answer": "neck"
  },
  {
    "question": "pleša",
    "answer": "bald"
  },
  {
    "question": "temni lasje",
    "answer": "dark hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "svetli lasje",
    "answer": "blond hair"
  },
  {
    "question": "skodrani",
    "answer": "curly"
  },
  {
    "question": "ravni",
    "answer": "straight"
  },
  {
    "question": "valoviti",
    "answer": "wavy"
  },
  {
    "question": "dolgi",
    "answer": "long"
  },
  {
    "question": "kratki (na ježka)",
    "answer": "crew cut"
  },
  {
    "question": "dva čopa",
    "answer": "pigtails"
  },
  {
    "question": "en čop",
    "answer": "ponytail"
  },
  {
    "question": "fru fru",
    "answer": "fringe"
  },
  {
    "question": "žalosten",
    "answer": "sad"
  },
  {
    "question": "jezen",
    "answer": "angry"
  },
  {
    "question": "ponosen",
    "answer": "proud"
  },
  {
    "question": "prestrašen",
    "answer": "scared"
  },
  {
    "question": "resen",
    "answer": "serious"
  },
  {
    "question": "vesel",
    "answer": "happy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem žalosten, jočem.",
    "answer": "When I'm sad, I cry."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem radoveden, vprašam.",
    "answer": "When I'm curious, I ask."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem zdolgočasen, spim.",
    "answer": "When I'm bored, I sleep."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem vesel, se smejim.",
    "answer": "When I'm happy, I smile."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem sramežljiv, se skrijem.",
    "answer": "When I'm shy, I hide."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem prestrašen, zakričim.",
    "answer": "When I'm scared, I scream."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem zaljubljen, se poljubim.",
    "answer": "When I'm loving, I kiss."
  },
  {
    "question": "Ko sem zmeden, skomignem z rameni.",
    "answer": "When I'm puzzled, I shrug."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoje oči?",
    "answer": "What can your eyes do? They can see."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoji zobje?",
    "answer": "What can your teeth do? They can chew."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoja ušesa?",
    "answer": "What can your ears do? They can hear."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoje roke?",
    "answer": "What can your arms do? They can hug."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoji prsti?",
    "answer": "What can your fingers do? They can touch."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko dela tvoj hrbet?",
    "answer": "What can your back do? It can bend."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoje noge?",
    "answer": "What can your legs do? They can run."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoja usta?",
    "answer": "What can your mouth do? It can kiss."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko dela tvoj nos?",
    "answer": "What can your nose do? It can smell."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko delajo tvoje dlani?",
    "answer": "What can your hands do? They can clap."
  },
  {
    "question": "Kaj lahko dela tvoja glava?",
    "answer": "What can your head do? It can nod."
  },
  {
    "question": "Z rokami lahko ploskam.",
    "answer": "I can clap with my hands."
  },
  {
    "question": "S prsti se lahko dotaknem.",
    "answer": "I can touch with my fingers."
  },
  {
    "question": "Z rokami lahko objamem.",
    "answer": "I can hug with my arms."
  },
  {
    "question": "Z zobmi lahko žvečim.",
    "answer": "I can chew with my teeth."
  },
  {
    "question": "S stopali lahko brcam.",
    "answer": "I can kick with my feet."
  },
  {
    "question": "S prsti na nogi hodim po prstih.",
    "answer": "I can tiptoe with my toes."
  },
  {
    "question": "Z glavo lahko prikimam.",
    "answer": "I can nod with my head."
  },
  {
    "question": "S hrbtom se lahko upognem.",
    "answer": "I can bend my back."
  }
]
